<resources>
  <string name="app_name">My MovieDB</string>

  <string name="movies">Movies</string>
  <string name="tv_shows">TV Shows</string>

  <string name="movie.a_star_is_born.title">A Star Is Born</string>
  <string name="movie.a_star_is_born.overview">Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling artist Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Ally\'s career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons.</string>

  <string name="movie.aquaman.title">Aquaman</string>
  <string name="movie.aquaman.overview">Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.</string>

  <string name="movie.avenger_infinity_war.title">Avengers: Infinity War</string>
  <string name="movie.avenger_infinity_war.overview">As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</string>

  <string name="movie.bird_box.title">Bird Box</string>
  <string name="movie.bird_box.overview">Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</string>

  <string name="movie.bohemian_rapsody.title">Bohemian Rapsody</string>
  <string name="movie.bohemian_rapsody.overview">Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock \'n\' roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury\'s increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.</string>

  <string name="movie.bumblebee.title">Bumblebee</string>
  <string name="movie.bumblebee.overview">On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken.  When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.</string>

  <string name="movie.creed_ii.title">Creed II</string>
  <string name="movie.creed_ii.overview">Between personal obligations and training for his next big fight against an opponent with ties to his family\'s past, Adonis Creed is up against the challenge of his life.</string>

  <string name="movie.deadpool.title">Deadpool</string>
  <string name="movie.deadpool.overview">Deadpool tells the origin story of former Special Forces operative turned mercenary Wade Wilson, who after being subjected to a rogue experiment that leaves him with accelerated healing powers, adopts the alter ego Deadpool. Armed with his new abilities and a dark, twisted sense of humor, Deadpool hunts down the man who nearly destroyed his life.</string>

  <string name="movie.how_to_train_your_dragon.title">How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</string>
  <string name="movie.how_to_train_your_dragon.overview">As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless’ discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup’s reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind.</string>

  <string name="movie.dragon_ball_super_broly.title">Dragon Ball Super: Broly</string>
  <string name="movie.dragon_ball_super_broly.overview">Earth is peaceful following the Tournament of Power. Realizing that the universes still hold many more strong people yet to see, Goku spends all his days training to reach even greater heights. Then one day, Goku and Vegeta are faced by a Saiyan called \'Broly\' who they\'ve never seen before. The Saiyans were supposed to have been almost completely wiped out in the destruction of Planet Vegeta, so what\'s this one doing on Earth? This encounter between the three Saiyans who have followed completely different destinies turns into a stupendous battle, with even Frieza (back from Hell) getting caught up in the mix</string>

  <string name="movie.glass.title">Glass</string>
  <string name="movie.glass.overview">In a series of escalating encounters, former security guard David Dunn uses his supernatural abilities to track Kevin Wendell Crumb, a disturbed man who has twenty-four personalities. Meanwhile, the shadowy presence of Elijah Price emerges as an orchestrator who holds secrets critical to both men.</string>

  <string name="movie.hunter_killer.title">Hunter Killer</string>
  <string name="movie.hunter_killer.overview">Captain Glass of the USS Arkansas discovers that a coup d\'état is taking place in Russia, so he and his crew join an elite group working on the ground to prevent a war.</string>

  <string name="tv_show.arrow.title">Arrow</string>
  <string name="tv_show.arrow.overview">After being double-crossed by Lyla, Oliver finds himself facing a life or death situation that seems very familiar. Laurel has the opportunity to make amends with the past.</string>

  <string name="tv_show.dragon_ball.title">Dragon Ball</string>
  <string name="tv_show.dragon_ball.overview">Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy whom he named Goku. Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died. The young and very strong boy was on his own, but easily managed. Then one day, Goku met a teenage girl named Bulma, whose search for the mystical Dragon Balls brought her to Goku\'s home. Together, they set off to find all seven and to grant her wish.</string>

  <string name="tv_show.fairy_tail.title">Fairy Tail</string>
  <string name="tv_show.fairy_tail.overview">Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of transportation. But Natsu isn\'t just any ordinary kid, he\'s a member of one of the world\'s most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail.</string>

  <string name="tv_show.family_guy.title">Family Guy</string>
  <string name="tv_show.family_guy.overview">Peter gets himself arrested to avoid Lois\' special Thanksgiving dinner; A secret that Stewie\'s been keeping from everyone is revealed.</string>

  <string name="tv_show.flash.title">Flash</string>
  <string name="tv_show.flash.overview">As Barry Allen stands on the threshold of his impending death in Crisis, his convictions are tested when the monstrous Dr. Ramsey Rosso infects The Flash with a mysterious, hallucinogenic contagion. Meanwhile, reporter Iris West-Allen uncovers a vast conspiracy.</string>

  <string name="tv_show.gotham.title">Gotham</string>
  <string name="tv_show.gotham.overview">Before there was Batman, there was GOTHAM. Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime world\'s greatest foes, a man whose reputation is synonymous with law and order. But what is known of Gordon\'s story and his rise from rookie detective to Police Commissioner? What did it take to navigate the multiple layers of corruption that secretly ruled Gotham City, the spawning ground of the world\'s most iconic villains? And what circumstances created them – the larger-than-life personas who would become Catwoman, The Penguin, The Riddler, Two-Face and The Joker?</string>

  <string name="tv_show.grey_anatomy.title">Grey Anatomy</string>
  <string name="tv_show.grey_anatomy.overview">Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle’s Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital.</string>

  <string name="tv_show.hanna.title">Hanna</string>
  <string name="tv_show.hanna.overview">This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film.</string>

  <string name="tv_show.iron_fist.title">Iron Fist</string>
  <string name="tv_show.iron_fist.overview">Danny Rand resurfaces 15 years after being presumed dead. Now, with the power of the Iron Fist, he seeks to reclaim his past and fulfill his destiny.</string>

  <string name="tv_show.naruto_shippuden.title">Naruto Shippuden</string>
  <string name="tv_show.naruto_shippuden.overview">Naruto had once lived a lonely existence, ostracized by everyone. But Iruka\'s words and his very presence have supported Naruto to this day. As Naruto\'s wedding nears, Iruka begins to lose sight of what he was to Naruto, and is unsure of what to say for his message.</string>
</resources>